idpielts.me 2018-03-22

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

IDP understands that privacy is important to you and is committed to complying with the National Privacy Principles (NPPS) which is contained in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (“Privacy Act”). Your access and use of this website is subject to this Privacy Policy and all applicable laws. By accessing and using this website, you accept and agree to this Privacy Policy without any limitation or qualification.

### What personal information does IDP collect?

(a) Electronic Forms  
If you subscribe to our website, the personal information we will collect from you includes your name, address, contact details, occupation and professional memberships. If you order any products from our website, we also collect your credit card details. We do not collect personal information that we do not need.

(b) Website traffic tracking  
When you visit our website, our server makes a record of your visit and logs the following information:  
– the number of page views (or page impressions) that occur on an IDP website  
– the number of unique visitors  
– how long these unique visitors (on average) spend on an IDP website, and  
– common entry and exit points to IDP sites.

### How does IDP use personal information?

We may use your personal information so that we can provide our services, fulfill any online orders, respond to your questions, inform students, institutions and other clients of developments in the services we provide (including events and opportunities to participate in projects/programs) and manage our internal business operations. IDP will not without your prior consent disclosure personal information collected about you on this website to any other party except in the case of our carriers to whom we supply your name and address as well as any particular delivery instructions you may have given us. Further, IDP does not sell, rent or trade your personal information to any other third parties except if required by law or permitted under the Privacy Act.

### Security

IDP takes reasonable steps to ensure the security of your personal information. We frequently update our anti-virus software to protect our systems from computer viruses. Further, all IDP employees are required, as a condition of employment, to treat personal information held by IDP as confidential. However, you should be aware that the internet is not a secure environment. We cannot protect personal information before it reaches us.

### Access to Personal Information

Under the Privacy Act, you have the right to seek access to your personal information handled by IDP.

### Accuracy of Information

Under the Privacy Act, you have the right to request us to update or correct your personal information when it is inaccurate, incomplete or out of date. If your personal details change, or you believe the information we hold about you is incorrect, please contact us so that we can update our records.

### Links

This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected on our website and may differ from the policies of other websites that you link to from this website. We recommend that you read the privacy policy of any website that you link to from our website.
